thebaseballcube.com 2007-06-22

# Privacy Policy - The Baseball Cube

The Baseball Cube understands that when you submit information about yourself to us that you wish for it to remain private and thus, we are committed to insuring that any information sent to us remains confidential. Any time we request specific information from you via a web form, we intend to use the data precisely for its intended outlined purpose. This document will further clarify our intentions. 

**Newsletter:** The Baseball Cube newsletter asks you to submit your email address to us via a web form. At no time will your email address be visible to site visitors nor will we be giving or selling your email away to other companies. The purpose of collecting addresses is to be able to send you periodical emails with information on our site and by providing us with that email, you are simply letting us know that you are okay with receiving this information. The information sent to you will be text only and will not contain viruses or inappropriate material.

**Affiliates:** The Baseball Cube has signed up with different affiliate programs on the Internet including Commission Junction and Amazon.Com. If a visitor to The Baseball Cube clicks on one of these links, the privacy policy of The Baseball Cube is no longer in effect. We are responsible for only the information that is submitted to our site through our web forms or email. Any information sent to third-party web sites, and it use, is completely out of the control of The Baseball Cube.

**Disclosure:** The Baseball Cube promises to keep all personal information confidential. Submitters email address, name, address and any other personal information will not visibly appear on the site. The exception is the sponsorship information submitted which is intended for use on the site. You will not receive unsolicited junk mail from any other company nor will you receive unsolicted random emails from us, unless to publicize a policy change on the site for those who hold a stake. At times, we may provide aggregate demographic information about our site to potential advertisers but under no circumstances, will we provide them with anything more.

**Third Party Advertising:** In addition to affiliate product advertisements on the site, we also include network advertisement programs that provide 3rd party ads not sought out immediately by The Baseball Cube. These 3rd party ads appear throughout the site and the same privacy policy applies to these networks as applies to the affiliates above.

**Third Party Cookies:** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

For questions about our privacy policy, contact us at [baseball@sports-wired.com](mailto:baseball@sports-wired.com)
